A Guide to the Government Affairs Foundation records FA1159
Rockefeller Archive Center
Government Affairs Foundation records
1953-1969
Rockefeller Archive Center
Government Affairs Foundation (New York)
FA1159
51.6 Cubic Feet 43 standard record storage boxes
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in two record groups by accession.
Conditions Governing Access
Record Group 1 is open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged materials may be restricted at the discretion of RAC. Record Group 2 remains restricted pending further processing.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records of the Government Affairs Foundation were donated to the Rockefeller Archive Center in 1981. The Rockefeller Family Archives (Room 5600) received the records that comprise Record Group 1 from the Government Affairs Foundation in 1968 and 1969. The Record Group 1 files were received by the Rockefeller Archive Center in 1981 and were accessioned on February 6, 1981 as Accession 1981:006.
Appraisal
The administration, finance, personnel, projects and studies records were initially appraised in June 1968. The publication and minute books were initially appraised in June 1969.
Scope and Contents
The collection is primarily comprised of project files, surveys, conference proceedings, studies, reports, administrative files, and a selection of vital records including meeting records, minutes, documents of record, and dissolution documents.
- Accession 1981:006, 1953-1969; 1; 23.7 Cubic Feet 19 standard record storage boxes and 2 letter document boxes.
  Scope and Contents
  The collection is primarily comprised of project files, surveys, conference proceedings, studies, reports, administrative files, and a selection of vital records including meeting records, minutes, documents of record, and dissolution documents.
  Arrangement
  Record Group 1 is arranged in six series as follows:
  Series 1: Administration
  Series 2: General
  Series 3: Projects
  Series 4: Publications
  Series 5: Minutes and Documents of Record
  Series 6: Personnel and Financial files
  - Administration, 1
    - Announcements - Change of Address, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Board of Direcors - General, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Board of Directors - Bolton, Howard A., 1964-1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Board of Directors - Boyer, Louise A., 1954-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Board of Directors - Goldstein, Nathaniel L., 1954-1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Board of Directors - Harrison, Wallace K., 1956-1959 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Board of Directors - Jamieson, Francis A., 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Board of Directors - Lockwood, John E., 1953-1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Board of Directors - Rockefeller, Rodman, 1954-1957 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Board of Directors - Siegesmund, Carl E., 1953-1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Board of Directors Meetings - Agendas for Meetings, 1954-1956 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Board of Directors Meetings - Notices of Meetings, 1953-1967 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Board of Directors Meetings - Proxies, 1958-1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Mr. Hodskin - Board of Directors Meetings, 1962-1967 (Box 1, Folder 14-18)
    - Charitable Organizations - Annual Report (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Exemption Application, 1954 (Form 1023) (Box 1, Folder 20-21)
    - Exemption - Albany 3 Percent Consumer Utility Tax (on Telephone) (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Exemption - New York City Sales Tax, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Exemption - Internal Revenue Audit, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 24-25)
    - Finances - Bookkeeeper, 1957-1968 (Box 1, Folder 26-30)
    - Finances - Brosnan, Daniel M., 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Finances - Budget, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Finances - Budget, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Finances - Budget, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Finances - Budget and Expenditures, 1958 March 13 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Finances - Budget, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Finances - Budget, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Finances - Budget - Preliminary Estimate, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Finances - Budget - January Revision of 1958, 1959 and 1960 Budgets, 1958-1960 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Finances - Budget Material (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Finances - Cash Statements, 1959-1968 (Box 2, Folder 41-42)
    - Finances - Comparison of Expenditures with Budget Proposals, 1960-1967 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Finances - Contributions Received from NAR and others, 1953-1968 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Finances - Treasurer - Hodgkin, John P., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Finances - Keebler, Philip F., 1953-1961 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Finances - Inventory (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Finances - Leases (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Finances - Library (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Organization of Foundation - American Foundation Information Service, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Organization of Foundation - Legal Documents (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Organization of Foundation - Organization, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Organization of Foundation - News Releases (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Organization of Foundation - Rockefeller, David, 1953-1957 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Procedures, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Office Space - 155 Washington Avenue, 1960-1966 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Office Space - 75 State Street (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Subscriptions, 1957-1968 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - General, 2
    - Arden House - American Assembly (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Correspondence - Applications for Grants, 1954-1968 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Correspondence - General, 1954-1968 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Correspondence - Form Letters, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Correspondence - Inquiries for Information, 1955-1968 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Correspondence - Inquiries for Information (Termination Notice Sent), 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 64-65)
    - Foundations - Reports, 1950-1955 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Governmental Research Association (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Hillenbrand, Bernard F., National Association of Counties, 1957-1964 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Indiana University (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Intergovernmental Relations, 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Keith, C. Allen, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Kellog - Symposium Columbia University, 1953 November 16-17 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Lieutenant Governors - Meeting in New York City, 1964 August 21 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - National Municipal League - Seattle Conference, 1955 July 24-27 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Program and Progress Reports, 1954-1957 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - General, 1956-1962 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - Special Studies - Report V, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1953-1959 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Speeches, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Rockefeller Public Service Fund, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Savell, Isabelle, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Projects, 3
    - Education Finance Bibliography (Burke) (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Health - Government Programs for the Improvement of the National Health (Study by Debevoise, Plimpton and McLean), 1953-1958 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - In-Service Training - Bibliography - Distribution - Acknowledgements, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - In-Service Training - Bibliography - Distribution and Mailing, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - In-Service Training - Bibliography - Front Matter, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - In-Service Training - Bibliography - General, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - In-Service Training - Bibliography - Joint Reference Library, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - In-Service Training - Bibliography - Mailing List (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - In-Service Training - Bibliography - Manuscripts (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - In-Service Training - Bibliography - Page Proofs (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - In-Service Training - Bibliography - Preparation, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - In-Service Training - Bibliography - Printing, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - In-Service Training - Bibliography - Requests for Copies, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - In-Service Training - Bibliography - Dr. Stout, 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - In-Service Training - Bibliography - University of California, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - In-Service Training - Conference - Meeting, 1966 March 2 (Box 6, Folder 97)
    - In-Service Training - Conference - Recording Tapes - Meetings, 1966 March 2 (Box 6, Folder 98)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - In-Service Training - Transcript of Meeting, 1966 March 2 (Box 6, Folder 99)
    - In-Service Training - Correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 6, Folder 100)
    - In-Service Training - Personnel, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 101)
    - In-Service Training - Publications, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 102)
    - In-Service Training - Survey, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - In-Service Training - Reports, 1964-1966 (Box 6, Folder 104-105)
    - In-Service Training Program - Association of Towns, 1961-1965 (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - In-Service Training Program - Conference of Mayors, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 107)
    - In-Service Training Program - County Officers Association (Box 6, Folder 108)
    - In-Service Training Program - Fire Training, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 109)
    - In-Service Training Program - Foreign Countries, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 110)
    - In-Service Training Program - League of California Cities (Box 6, Folder 111)
    - In-Service Training Program - Miscellaneous, 1964-1966 (Box 6, Folder 112)
    - In-Service Training Program - New York City, 1964-1966 (Box 7, Folder 113)
    - In-Service Training Program - Police Training, 1963-1965 (Box 7, Folder 114)
    - In-Service Training Program - School Boards Association, 1964-1966 (Box 7, Folder 115)
    - In-Service Training Program - Specialized Training, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 116)
    - In-Service Training Program - State Universities - Other States, 1958-1965 (Box 7, Folder 117)
    - In-Service Training Program - Publications and Reports (Box 7, Folder 118-120)
    - Local Government History - Dutch Period - Bibliography, 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 121)
    - Local Government History, 1963-1968 (Box 7, Folder 122)
    - Local Government History - Index Cards - Citations re: Police Function, General Overview, Indian Form of Government and Dutch Period (Box 20)
      Restricted - Confidential material
    - Metropolitan Series - Bibliography, 1954-1959 (Box 8, Folder 123)
    - Metropolitan Series - Bibliography Supplement, 1957-1964 (Box 8, Folder 124)
    - Metropolitan Series - Book on Metropolitan (Standard Work), 1955-1959 (Box 8, Folder 125)
    - Metropolitan Series - Digest of Surveys (Box 8, Folder 126)
    - Metropolitan Series - Partial Draft of book on Metropolitan Government (Box 19, Folder 264-265)
    - Conference on Metropolitan Area Problems (COMAP) - Bi-Monthly Bulletin, 1957-1965 (Box 9, Folder 127)
    - Conference on Metropolitan Area Problems (COMAP) - Board of Directors, 1956-1963 (Box 9, Folder 128)
    - Conference on Metropolitan Area Problems (COMAP) - California, 1951-1959 (Box 9, Folder 129)
    - Conference on Metropolitan Area Problems (COMAP) - Conferences - Future, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 130)
    - Conference on Metropolitan Area Problems (COMAP) - Cooperative Action - Plans and Comments, 1957-1962 (Box 9, Folder 131)
    - Conference on Metropolitan Area Problems (COMAP) - Cooperative Action, Proposals and Financing (Box 9, Folder 132)
    - Conference on Metropolitan Area Problems (COMAP) - Cooperative Committee, 1955 October 11 (Box 9, Folder 133)
    - Conference on Metropolitan Area Problems (COMAP) - Interim Subcommittee, 1955 December 5 (Box 9, Folder 134)
    - Conference on Metropolitan Area Problems (COMAP) - Interim Subcommittee, 1956 February 28 (Box 9, Folder 135)
    - Conference on Metropolitan Area Problems (COMAP) - Deming, George H., 1957-1962 (Box 9, Folder 136)
    - Conference on Metropolitan Area Problems (COMAP) - General, 1955-1959 (Box 9, Folder 137)
    - Conference on Metropolitan Area Problems (COMAP) - Meetings, Board of Directors, 1956 October 27 (Box 9, Folder 138)
    - Conference on Metropolitan Area Problems (COMAP) - Meetings, Board of Directors, 1957 June 6 (Box 9, Folder 139)
    - Conference on Metropolitan Area Problems (COMAP) - Meetings, Board of Directors, 1958 January 24 (Box 9, Folder 140)
    - Conference on Metropolitan Area Problems (COMAP) - Meetings, Board of Directors, 1959 December 11 (Box 9, Folder 141)
    - Conference on Metropolitan Area Problems (COMAP) - Metropolitan Research Study (Box 9, Folder 142)
    - Conference on Metropolitan Area Problems (COMAP) - New York State Conference, 1957-1958 (Box 9, Folder 143)
    - National Conference on Metropolitan Area Problems - Cooperative Committee and Interim Subcommittee, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 144)
    - National Conference on Metropolitan Area Problems - Dinner Meeting, 1955 March 17 (Box 9, Folder 145)
    - National Conference on Metropolitan Area Problems - Sady, Emil J., 1956 (Box 9, Folder 146)
    - National Conference on Metropolitan Area Problems - Conference Proceedings (East Lansing), 1956-1959 (Box 9, Folder 147)
    - National Conference on Metropolitan Area Problems - Conference Materials (East Lansing) (Box 10, Folder 148-150)
    - National Conference on Metropolitan Area Problems - Roundtable Questions, 1958-1960 (Box 10, Folder 151)
    - County Project, New York State Metropolitan Problems (Box 10, Folder 152)
    - County Project, New York State Metropolitan Problems - Manuscript (Box 10, Folder 153)
    - Metro - General - America Assembly, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 154)
    - Metro - General - Arden House - Conference on Metropolitan Area Problems, 1957 September 21-23 (Box 11, Folder 155)
    - Metro - General - Bollens, John C., 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 156)
    - Metro - General - Book Reviews, 1956-1957 (Box 11, Folder 157)
    - Metro - General - Boston University - Bureau of Public Administration, 1956-1958 (Box 11, Folder 158)
    - Metro - General - Brown, Louis D. - Report on Metropolitan Area Problems, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 159)
    - Metro - General - Cassella, William N. (Box 11, Folder 160)
    - Metro - General - Chatters, Carl H. (City of Chicago), 1953-1959 (Box 11, Folder 161)
    - Metro - General - City College of New York - New York Area Research Council (Box 11, Folder 162)
    - Metro - General - City of Buffalo (Box 11, Folder 163)
    - Metro - General - City of Boston (Box 11, Folder 164)
    - Metro - General - City of Cleveland (Box 11, Folder 165)
    - Metro - General - City of Detroit, 1954-1956 (Box 11, Folder 166)
    - Metro - General - City of Los Angeles, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 167)
    - Metro - General - City of Miami, 1955-1957 (Box 11, Folder 168)
    - Metro - General - City of Milwaukee, 1955-1957 (Box 11, Folder 169)
    - Metro - General - City of Montreal, 1953-1954 (Box 11, Folder 170)
    - Metro - General - City of New York (Hal Burton; Janowski of City College), 1956-1957 (Box 11, Folder 171)
    - Metro - General - City of Richmond (Horace Edwards), 1954-1955 (Box 11, Folder 172)
    - Metro - General - City of St. Louis (Mrs. Spencer Vanderbilt), 1955 (Box 11, Folder 173)
    - Metro - General - City of Seattle (Eden Thirkield), 1956 (Box 11, Folder 174)
    - Metro - General - City of Syracuse (Executive Director Grimm, City Planning Commission), 1956 (Box 11, Folder 175)
    - Metro - General - City of Toronto (Gardiner), 1954-1956 (Box 11, Folder 176)
    - Metro - General - Conferences - Miscellaneous, 1953-1957 (Box 11, Folder 177)
    - Metro - General - Cooperative Action, Plans and Comments (Box 11, Folder 178)
    - Metro - General - Cooperative Action, Proposals for Financing, 1954-1956 (Box 11, Folder 179)
    - Metro - General - Correspondence, General, 1953-1960 (Box 11, Folder 180)
    - Metro - General - Council of Metropolitan Regional Organizations, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 181)
    - Metro - General - Council of State Governments, 1955-1958 (Box 11, Folder 182)
    - Metro - General - Dowdy, Homer E. (Flint, Michigan), 1955-1957 (Box 12, Folder 183)
    - Metro - General - Federal-State Joint Action Committee, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 184)
    - Metro - General - Fordham - Dr. Jefferson B. - Dean, Pennsylvania Law School, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 185)
    - Metro - General - Harvard Graduate School of Public Administration (Box 12, Folder 186)
    - Metro - General - Harvard University - Metropolitan New York Project, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 187)
    - Metro - General - Illinois - Northeastern Illinois Metropolitan Area Local Governmental Services Commission, 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 188)
    - Metro - General - Institute of Public Administration, 1956-1959 (Box 12, Folder 189)
    - Metro - General - Jones, Victor, 1954-1959 (Box 12, Folder 190)
    - Metro - General - Kenmore, Town of Tonawanda, Municipal Research Commission, 1955-1957 (Box 12, Folder 191)
    - Metro - General - Larson, Donald R., 1956-1958 (Box 12, Folder 192)
    - Metro - General - Metropolitan Areas - Statistical Data, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 193)
    - Metro - General - National Association of Home Builders, 1956-1959 (Box 12, Folder 194)
    - Metro - General - National Municipal League, 1956-1959 (Box 12, Folder 195)
    - Metro - General - New York Legislative Committee on Metropolitan Areas, 1957-1960 (Box 12, Folder 196)
    - Metro - General - New York Metropolitan Region Study (by School of Public Administration, Harvard), 1954-1959 (Box 12, Folder 197)
    - Metro - General - Problems in Metropolitan Areas, 1953-1958 (Box 12, Folder 198)
    - Metro - General - Reed, Dr. Thomas H. (Box 12, Folder 199)
    - Metro - General - Skinner, Calvin (Cincinnati Bureau of Governmental Research), 1953-1955 (Box 12, Folder 200)
    - Metro - General - Study - Tri State Area: New Jersey, New York and Connecticut, 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 201)
    - Metro - General - Van Loon, Henry, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 202)
    - Metro - General - Washington, D.C. Metropolitan Area, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 203)
    - Metro - General - Wayne University - Social Science Research Center (Box 12, Folder 204)
    - Metro - General - Woodbury, Coleman, 1955-1957 (Box 12, Folder 205)
    - Metro - Handbook on Metropolitan Surveys (Box 12, Folder 206)
    - Metro - New York State Study, 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 207-209)
    - Metro - Popular Pamphlet, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 210)
    - Metro - Public Attitudes, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 211)
    - Metro - Public Health Project (Box 13, Folder 212)
    - Metro - Publications - General, 1955-1959 (Box 13, Folder 213)
    - Metro - Publications - Request for, 1957-1965 (Box 13, Folder 214)
    - Metro - Roster Project, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 215)
    - Metro - Television Series on Metropolitan Problems, 1956-1959 (Box 13, Folder 216)
    - State Agencies for Local Government - Bibliography (Box 13, Folder 217)
    - State Agencies for Local Government - Correspondence - General, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 218)
    - State Agencies for Local Government - Correspondence - Alabama - Kansas, 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 219)
    - State Agencies for Local Government - Correspondence - Kentucky - Missouri, 1960-1962 (Box 13, Folder 220)
    - State Agencies for Local Government - Correspondence - Montana - North Dakota, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 221)
    - State Agencies for Local Government - Correspondence - Ohio - South Dakota, 1960-1961 (Box 13, Folder 222)
    - State Agencies for Local Government - Correspondence - Pennsylvania, 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 223)
    - State Agencies for Local Government - Correspondence - Tennessee - Wyoming, 1960-1961 (Box 13, Folder 224)
    - Tax and Debt Limit Study - Acknowledgments, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 225)
    - Tax and Debt Limit Study - Advisory Committee on Intergovernmental Relations, 1961-1962 (Box 14, Folder 226)
    - Tax and Debt Limit Study - Bird, Frederick L., 1955-1964 (Box 14, Folder 227)
    - Tax and Debt Limit Study - Distribution, 1964-1966 (Box 14, Folder 228)
    - Tax and Debt Limit Study - Front Material, 1964-1969 (Box 14, Folder 229)
    - Tax and Debt Limit Study - General, 1955-1962 (Box 14, Folder 230-231)
    - Tax and Debt Limit Study - Goldstein, Judd and Gurfein - Report (Box 14, Folder 232)
    - Tax and Debt Limit Study - Preparation, 1959-1965 (Box 14, Folder 233)
    - Tax and Debt Limit Study - Printing, 1963-1966 (Box 14, Folder 234)
    - Tax and Debt Limit Study - Public Administration Service, 1961-1962 (Box 15, Folder 235)
    - Tax and Debt Limit Study - Requests for Copies, 1966-1969 (Box 15, Folder 236)
    - Welfare Study - Administration (Box 15, Folder 237)
    - Welfare Study - Administration - Rules, Regulations and Reports (Box 15, Folder 238)
    - Welfare Study - Award by Governmental Research Association (Box 15, Folder 239)
    - Welfare Study - Congressional Record, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 240)
    - Welfare Study - Distribution, 1955-1958 (Box 15, Folder 241)
    - Welfare Study - Federal Commission on Intergovernmental Relations Study Committee on Federal Aid to Welfare, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 242)
    - Welfare Study - Griffenhagen (Box 15, Folder 243)
    - Welfare Study - Judd and Gurfein - "Effect on State Constitutions upon Proposed Deposits by the States in Old Age and Survivors Insurance Fund" Report (Box 15, Folder 244)
    - Welfare Study - Lutz, Edward A. (Box 15, Folder 245)
    - Welfare Study - OASI - Clippings (Box 15, Folder 246)
    - Welfare Study - OASI - Correspondence - General, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 247)
    - Welfare Study - OASI - Duncan MacIntyre memorandum (Box 15, Folder 248)
    - Welfare Study - OASI - Report (Box 15, Folder 249)
    - Welfare Study - OASI - Statistics (Box 15, Folder 250)
    - Welfare Study - Ownership of Property by Recipients (Box 16, Folder 251)
    - Welfare Study - Pamphlets (Box 15, Folder 252)
    - Welfare Study - Report (Box 15, Folder 253)
    - Welfare Study - Report on Block Grants (Box 15, Folder 254)
    - Welfare Study - Report on Financial and Statistical Data (Box 15, Folder 255)
    - Welfare Study - Reports - Estimate of Cost of Reports (Box 15, Folder 256)
    - Welfare Study - Statistical Material (Box 16, Folder 257-258)
    - Welfare Study - Statistical Material - Expenditures for Administration by Source of Funds (Box 16, Folder 259)
    - Welfare Study - Statistical Material - Public Assistance Payments by Source of Funds (Box 16, Folder 260)
    - Welfare Study - Statistical Material - Public Assistance Trends in Federal, State and Local Shares (Box 16, Folder 261)
    - Welfare Study - Study Outlines and Memoranda (Box 16, Folder 262)
    - Welfare Study - Wells, John A. - Speech at Hobart College (Box 16, Folder 263)
  - Publications, 4
    - Publications (Box 17)
    - Publications (Box 18)
  - Minutes and Documents of Record, 5
    - Meeting Minutes, 1953-1969 (Box 18)
    - Documents of Record (Box 18)
    - Dissolution of Foundation (Box 18)
  - Personnel and Financial files, 6
    - Employee records, 1954-1969 (Box 21)
      Restricted - Personnel material
    - Payroll records (Box 21)
    - Financial records (Box 21)